distance-fromto.com 2018-01-26

# Calculator from Map with car or flight from city to city Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Last revised April 13, 2016 

Thank you for visiting distance-fromto.com (the "Site") and reviewing the Privacy Policy of distance-fromto limited. ("distance-fromto" or "we" or "us"). It is important to us that you understand what information we collect when you visit the Site either from a computer or a mobile device and what we may do with that information, so we have laid it all out here for you. This Privacy Policy also covers the collection of data from applications on mobile devices.

By using this Site you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy, and you signify your assent to all of the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. If you do not agree with any terms of this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use please do not use this Site or submit any personal information. Please take care to read our Privacy Policy to be sure you are informed about how your information may be used. Please also read our Terms of Use.

Getting to know you

When do we ask for PII?

Google Services we are using. We use Google Analytics to help analyze use of our website. This analytical tool uses 'cookies', which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. 

The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors' use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity for this website. To find out more about cookies, including how to control and delete them, visit www.allaboutcookies.org, or to opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. We will not (and will not allow any third party) to use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any personally identifiable information of visitors to our site. 

We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any personally identifying information from any source as part of our use of the Google statistical analytics tool. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither ourselves nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. 

Doubleclick ad servers. To serve advertisements on the Site, we make use of DoubleClick services, a Google company. These services are offered from out of the European Union. To serve the correct advertisements, we provide DoubleClick with location data. DoubleClick warrants safety and protection of the information provided as described in the "Safe Harbor" Privacy Principles and Google will only use this data to honor the agreement between Google and us. (Data will not be used by Google for own purpose) 

Cookies from Advertising Partner. Please note that our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control. 

How we use what we know

Do we use analytics companies? We may provide some non-personal information to others who help us understand how you use the Site 

Going Public and Being Social

Clicking through. This Privacy Policy applies to distance-fromto and our Site only. Our Site contains links to or integrations with other sites, whose information practices may be different than ours. Before you click through to another site, you should read that site's privacy notice, since we have no control over and take no responsibility for information that is submitted to, or collected by other sites.

Is There Anything Else I Need to Know?

Changing Our Policy. This Privacy Policy is subject to change. We will prominently post a notice on the Site when there are material changes in the way we treat PII. You should periodically check back and review this Privacy Policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and with whom we share it.

Security Measures

While distance-fromto has security measures to help protect the information under our control, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

Contact Us

Don't be shy! If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or information that you have submitted to us or if you would like to do any of the following:
